http://www.arlingtoncareerinstitute.edu/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); To send periodic emails; To contact you in response to your interest in our school. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
By filling out this form, you understand that Arlington Career Institute will utilize this information to contact you to provide more information about Arlington Career Institute by a variety of methods including phone (both mobile or home, dialed manually or automatically), email, mail, and text message. Additionally, calls may be monitored or recorded for quality assurance.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We may transfer to 3rd parties your personally identifiable information. This includes trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Appending Your Personal Information
When collecting your personal information on our site we are attempting to contact you in response to your interest in our school or program. We may append your personal information, including but not limited to: email address, phone number, name and mailing address. This information is appended by a 3rd party outsourced for this particular purpose.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 09/05/13.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
© 2019 ACI. All right reserved.Privacy PolicyDisclosuresSitemap
